Rebel: Captain. She's highly trained. Deception. Infiltration. Extraction.
Rebel: She's special forces.
Captain: Iden Versio.
Captain: Inferno Squad.
Captain: **Commander** Versio.  You must be important.
Captain: Look at me.
Captain: So let's talk facts. That's what I'm here for. You have the activation code, I've got the ability to help you out.
Captain: Just give me the code.
Captain: You know we could really use someone like you.
Captain: Just help me and I'll help you, it's that easy.
Captain: I'm going to get what I want eventually. My best technicians are slicing into your droid right now.
Captain: Think on my offer. All I want is the code.
Captain: The Empire's time has come. You don't have to go down with it.
Iden: You're right.
Iden: The Empire's time has come.
Iden: VZ-626.